Here's how you can make your clawed code
output or really any agent output a lot
more readable and easier to work with.
Recently, I've been talking about this
extra little bit that I add to prompts
saying, "Be extremely concise. Sacrifice
grammar for the sake of concision. This
turns large prompts into really nice
human readable format." And so I thought
to myself, why don't I add this into my
Claude code global claude.md file?
Because then I'll get much more concise
feedback coming from Claude. So I
decided to do a test. I found an error
that I needed Claude to debug for me and
I ran it without the extra command to
sacrifice its grammar. We can see that
straight away it starts outputting kind
of paragraphs for me. This is still
pretty short and easy to scan, but it's
still not as clean as it could be. I
think in the concise version, I get ESM
CGS mismatch. Let me check the build
output and config. Very direct. It
starts using nice little headers, too.
Root cause found. React 19
incompatibility with ink 4.1.0. Here's
another one. Still same error, but the
biggest difference is in the final
summary. This is without the concise
instruction where it gives me a fair
chunk of stuff, a little mini article to
read here. Whereas in the concise
version, it really is just a few words
here. A couple of headings, a little
list, and we get the information faster.
Now, of course, if I need to follow this
up with extra questions, I can. Under
the hood, the LLM still has the same
understanding of what it's done, but I
prefer this concise summary as the first
thing I receive. And here's what I have
in my claw. MD file. When reporting
information to me, be extremely concise
and sacrifice grammar for the sake of
concision.